commonbond.co 2019-04-29

# Privacy Policy | CommonBond

## Introduction

Welcome to CommonBond. This Privacy Statement describes how CommonBond collects, receives and shares information about you from our website and any off-line communications we may have with you, e.g. emails, telephone calls, text messages and personal communication, located at http://commonbond.co. This Privacy Policy, together with our Terms of Use govern your use of our website and our collection and use of your information.

## How does CommonBond work?

CommonBond offers loans for current undergraduate and graduate students, refinancing loans for people who have already graduated and contributions processing for people participating in their employer’s student loan benefits program. Loans are originated by CommonBond Lending, LLC.  

## What information does CommonBond collect from visitors to this website?  

CommonBond collects the following information from students, graduates, and visitors to our website:  

  * information you provide on our website such as contact information, school affiliation or feedback; and

  * basic traffic information about your visit such as IP address, host name and pages on our site visited.

  * loan application information such as social security number, income, and assets loan decisions. Such information may be shared with a partner bank.  

  * Existing student loan information such as existing balances and loan servicer information.  

We use third parties to gather your data from financial institutions. By using our service, you grant our third-party provider the right, power, and authority to act on your behalf to access and transmit your personal and financial information from the relevant financial institution according to the terms of our third-party provider's privacy policy.  
‍  
We do not collect personally identifiable information from website visitors who do not voluntarily submit such information. However, information collected from prior visits could be associated with personally identifiable information if you later submit such information to us.  

## Registered users

If you create a registered account on our website, we will collect information from you, including:

Name;  
Email Address; and  
Password.

## Cookies

We may use cookies and similar technologies such as web beacons to support the functionality of our customer portal, monitor traffic patterns and collect information about your previous visits to our web site.  

## Children and privacy

This website is not intended for use by children. If you are under 18, you may use this website only with the involvement of a parent or guardian. If you are a parent or guardian and believe that we may have inadvertently collected personal information from your child, please notify us immediately by sending an email to [info@commonbond.co](mailto:%20info@commonbond.co).

## How does CommonBond use information collected from visitors to this website?  

We use information collected from website visitors to improve the content and browsing experience of our website, to provide information regarding our products to you, and respond to you. This information is not sold or disclosed to non-affiliated third parties for marketing purposes, however we may contact you with marketing offers. CommonBond may disclose information collected from website visitors to:  

  * trusted services providers who work on our behalf, who do not have independent use of the information we disclose to them, and who have agreed to adhere to the rules set forth in the privacy statement;  

  * alert you to new features, products, events, or services;  

  * make other marketing offers that we think may be of interest of you;  

  * third parties as required by law, such as to comply with a subpoena or similar legal process  

  * third parties as we deem necessary, based on our good faith belief, (i) to protect our rights, your safety or the safety of others, (ii) to investigate fraud, or (iii) to respond to a government request; and  

  * third parties in conjunction with a merger, acquisition or sale of CommonBond. If CommonBond is involved in a merger, acquisition, or sale of all or a portion of its assets, you will be notified via email and/or a prominent notice on our website of any change in ownership or uses of this information, as well as any choices you may have regarding this information. Information obtained about loan applications and decisions from our partner bank may be used to improve our services or offer additional services. Use of information obtained from a partner bank will be used in accordance with the bank's privacy policy.  

## Remarketing

This website uses Google AdWords as a third party remarketing service to advertise across the internet to previous visitors of our website. Third-party remarketing services including Google, will use cookies and pixel tags (action tags) on your web browser to collect non-identifiable information about your visits and interaction with our website and display advertisements based on these past visits. The advertisements could be in the form of an advertisement on a Google search results page, a site in the Google Display Network, a banner or link. You can set preferences for how Google advertises to you using the [Google Ad Settings page](https://adssettings.google.com/authenticated) or opt out of a third-party vendor’s use of cookies by visiting the Network Advertising Initiative [opt-out page](https://www.networkadvertising.org/choices/). If you want to you can opt-out page of interest-based advertising entirely by changing your cookie settings or permanently using a browser plugin.

## Opt out

You may choose to opt-out of receiving unrequested communications by clicking “unsubscribe” of a given communication or by emailing [info@commonbond.co](mailto:%20info@commonbond.co).

## Security

We are concerned about safeguarding the confidentiality of your information. We provide physical, administrative, and technical safeguards to protect the information we collect and maintain.  

## Changes

This Privacy Statement may be updated from time to time for any reason. We will notify you of any changes to our Privacy Statement by posting the new Privacy Statement here, http://commonbond.co/privacy-policy. Please consult this Privacy Statement regularly for any changes.

## Your consent

By using our website, you consent to the collection, processing and storage of information as described in this Privacy Statement. Processing activities may take place in the United States. If you reside outside of the United States, your information may be transferred to, and processed and stored in, the United States or other jurisdictions in accordance with applicable law in that jurisdiction. If you do not agree to these terms, do not use this website.  

## Notice of privacy rights

Customers may access, review and/or correct all their personally identifiable information that we collect online by sending an email to [info@commonbond.co](mailto:%20info@commonbond.co) with a subject heading "Customer Choice Privacy Notice" And allow thirty (30) days for a response.

CommonBond, Inc.  
524 Broadway, 6th Floor  
New York, NY, 10012  
United States of America

## Contact us

If you have any questions about how we collect, store and use your information, you may contact us by e-mailing us at [info@commonbond.co](mailto:%20info@commonbond.co).  

## Vermont customers

We will not disclose nonpublic personal financial information about you to nonaffiliated third parties (other than as permitted by law) unless you authorize us to make that disclosure. Your authorization must be in writing or, if you agree, in electronic form.
